Guide to the Horace Dwight Taft Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1888-1983; Series I; 18.5' (45 boxes)
  - Taft School
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 339)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1975 January-December (Box 28, Folder 340-341)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 342)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1975 January-December (Box 29, Folder 343-344)
    - Taft Trustee Nominating Committee, 1975-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 345)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1976 Jan, 1976 April-October (Box 29, Folder 346-347)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-December (Box 29, Folder 348-349)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 350)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1977 January-May (Box 29, Folder 351)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1977 August-December (Box 30, Folder 352)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 353)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 354)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1978 January-Feb, 1978 May-September (Box 30, Folder 355-356)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 357)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 358)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1979 February-May, 1979 October-December (Box 30, Folder 359-360)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 361)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1979 February-Jun, 1979 September-December (Box 31, Folder 362-363)
    - Board of Trustees meeting minutes, 1980 January-May, 1980 August-December (Box 31, Folder 364-365)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 366)
    - Reports and miscellaneous material, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 367)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous material, 1981-1983, undated (Box 31, Folder 368)
  - United States
    - Department of Energy
      - Program budget
        - FY 1977, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 369)
        - FY 1978, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 370)
        - FY 1979, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 371)
        - FY 1980, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 372)
        - FY 1980, 1980, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 373-374)
        - FY 1980 (Box 32, Folder 375)
        - FY 1981, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 376)
        - FY 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 377-378)
        - FY 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 379-381)
      - Review, 1982, undated (Box 32, Folder 382)
  - Universities Research Association, 1972-1976, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 383)
  - University of Chicago, 1979-1983 (Box 32, Folder 384)
  - Writings
    - Preprints and reprints
      - 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 385)
      - 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 386)
      - 1963-1976 (Box 33, Folder 387-391)
      - 1978 (Box 33, Folder 392)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 393-396)
      - undated (Box 33, Folder 397)
      - undated (Box 34, Folder 398-400)
    - Speeches
      - Freshmen addresses: Yale College, 1968-1978, undated (Box 34, Folder 401-405)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973, undated, 1975-1979 (Box 34, Folder 406-407)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 35, Folder 408-409)
      - Taft School commencement address, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 410)
  - Yale files
    - Admissions Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 411)
    - Alumni, 1962-1965 (Box 35, Folder 412)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 413)
    - Appointment and salary letters, 1958-1983 (Box 35, Folder 414)
    - Board of Permanent Officers of Yale College, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 415)
    - Brewster, Kingman, 1975, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 416)
    - Collaborative research, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 417)
    - Committee on Academic Computing, 1981-1982 Apr, 1982 May-Oct, 1982 November-1983, undated (Box 35, Folder 418-420)
    - Committee on Energy Conservation, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 421)
    - Committee on Energy Conservation, 1979-1982, undated (Box 36, Folder 422-430)
    - Committee on Teaching and Learning, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 431)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 36, Folder 432-434)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 435)
    - Davenport College, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 436)
    - Davenport College: correspondence, 1966-1970 May, 1970 June-1971, undated (Box 37, Folder 437-439)
    - Davenport College: letters of congratulation, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 440)
    - Dean of Yale College: letters of congratulation, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 441-442)
    - Education of women, 1980-1981, undated (Box 37, Folder 443-444)
    - Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 445)
    - Faculty meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 37, Folder 446-449)
    - Faculty meetings, 1965-1972, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 450-460)
    - Freshman advisor, 1958, 1964-1965, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 461-463)
    - Freshman advisor, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 464)
    - German Exchange Fellowship Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 465)
    - Graduate School, 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 466)
    - Grants and contracts, 1979-1982 (Box 39, Folder 467)
    - Joint meetings of the Boards of Permanent Officers of Yale College and Graduate School, 1965-1966, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 468)
    - Junior faculty search, 1977-1978, undated (Box 39, Folder 469-470)
    - Letters of recommendation, 1977-1982, undated (Box 39, Folder 471-473)
    - Mathematics curriculum, 1961-1964, undated (Box 39, Folder 474)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1952-1959, 1966, 1972, undated (Box 39, Folder 475)
    - National Science Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 476)
    - Physics Department, 1963-1967, 1972-1982 (Box 39, Folder 477)
    - Provost, Office of, 1980, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 478-479)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1969-1970, undated (Box 40, Folder 480)
    - Sarai Ribicoff Award, undated (Box 40, Folder 481)
    - Senior faculty search, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 482-483)
    - Sophomore advisor, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 484)
    - Summer programs, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 485)
    - Tenure faculty meetings, 1963-1965 Nov, 1965 December-1966, 1977-1982, undated (Box 40, Folder 486-493)
    - Tobin Committee. Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Appointments, 1965, 1976-1980 September-Dec, 1981-1982, undated (Box 41, Folder 494-501)
    - Yale Accelerator Users Group: budget, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 502)
    - Yale Accelerator Users Group: budget, 1979, undated (Box 42, Folder 503)
    - Yale Accelerator Users Group: personnel, 1980-1982, undated (Box 42, Folder 504)
    - Yale College
      - Dean's Office, 1977-1980 Aug, 1980 September-1982, undated (Box 42, Folder 505-506)
      - Faculty meetings, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 507-508)
      - Teaching evaluation form, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 509)
  - Correspondence
    - 1952-1957 (Box 42, Folder 510-515)
    - 1958-1968 (Box 43, Folder 516-529)
    - 1968-1977 (Box 44, Folder 530-543)
    - 1978-1983, undated (Box 45, Folder 544-550)
- Teaching Files, 1941-1982; Series II; 3.75' (9 boxes)
  This series contains alphabetically arranged teaching files.
  - Early concentration physics, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Fermi: quantum mechanics notes, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Graduate courses, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Graduate student data, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Graduate student records, 1963-1964, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Graduate students, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - HEP graduate students, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953, undated, 1954-1961-1962, undated, 1962, undated, 1968-1969, undated (Box 46, Folder 9-12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976, undated, 1981, undated, 1965, 1982, undated (Box 47, Folder 13-16)
  - Physics 14: class lists, exams, etc., 1963, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 17-18)
  - Physics 14: exams, etc., 1965-1971 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Physics 14a, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Physics 14b: lecture notes, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Physics 15b and 14a, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Physics 15b, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Physics 22: Davenport seminar, 1952-1963 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Physics 22, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 25-26)
  - Physics 24: class lists, schedules, and exams, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Physics 24a: problems and exams, 1964, undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Physics 24b: problems, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Physics 24b: lectures, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Physics 25, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Physics 34b, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Physics 34b, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Physics 37b, undated (Box 49, Folder 34-39)
  - Physics 37b: problems, 1957-1962 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Physics 50, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Physics 106, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Physics 127a, 1963-1965, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 43-48)
  - Physics 127b, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Physics 127b, undated (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Physics 146: problems and exams, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 51-53)
  - Physics 150a, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Physics 180a, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Physics 180a: exams, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 56-57)
  - Physics 180a: lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 58-59)
  - Physics 180a: problems, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Physics 180a: problems, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 61-62)
  - Physics 180: problems and exams, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 63-64)
  - Physics 180a: review lectures, undated (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - Physics 180: section, undated (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - Physics 181b, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - Physics 181b: exams, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 68-69)
  - Physics 181b: exams and enrollment, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - Physics 181b: lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 71-73)
  - Physics 181b: lectures, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 74-75)
  - Physics 181b: problems, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 76-77)
  - Physics 181b: problems and exams, 1980-1982 (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Physics 181b: section, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - Physics 181b: syllabi, etc., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - Physics 200a, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 81)
  - Physics 201b, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 82)
  - Physics 211, undated (Box 53, Folder 83)
  - Physics comprehensive exam, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 84)
  - Physics curriculum, 1968, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 85-86)
  - Physics departmental examinations, 1941-1968, 1964-1969 (Box 54, Folder 87-88)
  - Physics labs, undated (Box 54, Folder 89-90)
  - Physics majors, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 91)
  - Thesis proposals, 1968, undated (Box 54, Folder 92-93)
  - "The Tippy Top", 1952-1953, 1967, undated (Box 54, Folder 94)
- Physics Files, 1947-1983; Series III; 12.25' (31 boxes)
  This series contains physics project files arranged as they were received from Taft's office.
  - Vertex routines
    - Notes, 1978, undated (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - HDVERT, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Line and vertex fitting, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - YVERT, 1969, 1975, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - SVERT and VERTEX, 1966-1967, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Spark chamber experiment, 1976-1979, undated (Box 55, Folder 7-9)
  - Hyperon beam
    - Miscellaneous material, 1978-1982, undated (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    - Leptonic decays of hyperons, 1969, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Internal π+ beam: Rosenfeld, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Σ analysis, 1961, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - K- meson, 1957-1958, undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Alvarez group, 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - YAP2 flow charts, 1965, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - YAP flow charts, 1964, undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - YAPR calculations, undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - GUTS, 1959-1962, 1967, undated (Box 56, Folder 21-22)
  - GUTS flow charts, 1962-1964, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Yale-PDP1: floating point package, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Count, undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - p4 cmΣ, undated (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory 1979 Dec 10: E-400 prop. neutral beam data, 1975-1979, undated (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Relativistic decay kinematics, undated (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Toroidal magnets, undated (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Drawing of proton-east, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Relativistic transformation, 1951, undated (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1976-1980, undated, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 32-33)
  - YACK flow charts, undated (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Beam 1 calculations, undated (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - SHUNT, 1967, undated (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - PANG, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Willis' K2 events, undated (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Equipment: microscopes, 1953-1957, undated (Box 57, Folder 39-40)
  - Talk at O.B., undated (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Analysis data: 3.3 Bev/6p experiment, 1961, undated (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - p experiment, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - p experiment, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Department of Energy contract, 1978-1982 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Zeller and Cooper, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - LeCroy Research Systems Corporation, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - LeCroy Research Systems Corporation [CAMAC electronics?], undated (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Stream chamber optical constants, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Circular A-21, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Polynomial FIT, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Experiment 630, 1980-1982 (Box 58, Folder 52-53)
  - Fastbus, 1979-1982 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - E 360, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - PDPI, 1961-1963, undated (Box 58, Folder 56-57)
  - CORE storage, undated (Box 58, Folder 58)
  - CELL + AHR, undated (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - Fortran CAL: routines, 1965, undated (Box 58, Folder 60)
  - TFLGUP, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 61)
  - PRPE, 1973, undated (Box 58, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1973, undated (Box 59, Folder 63)
  - KMVET, undated (Box 59, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 59, Folder 65)
  - TVGP-YACK operating instructions, undated (Box 59, Folder 66)
  - PEPR machine language, undated (Box 59, Folder 67)
  - o-w display, 1970, undated (Box 59, Folder 68)
  - FACONT, undated (Box 59, Folder 69)
  - GAINS, DTPROS, etc., 1970,undated (Box 59, Folder 70)
  - WIND (for TVGP), 1968, undated (Box 59, Folder 71)
  - Fortran film, 1966, undated (Box 59, Folder 72)
  - Fiducial coordinates, 1967, undated (Box 59, Folder 73)
  - FOCUS set-up routines, undated (Box 59, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 75)
  - KMTAV, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 76)
  - Parameters, undated (Box 59, Folder 77)
  - CLOOK F4 and MACRO, undated (Box 59, Folder 78)
  - AREASC, 1965, undated (Box 59, Folder 79)
  - K- bookkeeping, 1967, undated (Box 59, Folder 80)
  - MOPE, undated (Box 59, Folder 81)
  - TUPRT and TUCAL, undated (Box 59, Folder 82)
  - SUB-LIB, undated (Box 59, Folder 83)
  - MLIBS, 1968, undated (Box 59, Folder 84)
  - MLIBS, undated (Box 59, Folder 85)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1963, undated (Box 59, Folder 86)
  - Alvarez programming group, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 87)
  - 709 utility programs, undated (Box 60, Folder 88)
  - 6600 tape conversion, undated (Box 60, Folder 89)
  - Duplicate PDP-1 program write-ups, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 90)
  - Joe Lach paper to magnetic tape, 1968, undated (Box 60, Folder 91)
  - PDP-1: systems-level software, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 92)
  - PDP-1: core 2, undated (Box 60, Folder 93)
  - SAW, undated (Box 60, Folder 94)
  - RING, 1969, undated (Box 60, Folder 95)
  - Rtp, undated (Box 60, Folder 96)
  - Bookkeeping system, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 97)
  - PDP-10 graphics routines, undated (Box 60, Folder 98)
  - Telescope problem, 1979, undated (Box 60, Folder 99)
  - ION, 1968, undated (Box 60, Folder 100)
  - Cluster analysis, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 101)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center and Bevatron, 1965-1971, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 102)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1968-1969, undated (Box 60, Folder 103)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 61, Folder 104)
  - Yale High Energy Accelerator, 1962-1963 (Box 61, Folder 105-106)
  - Streamer chamber, 1970, undated (Box 61, Folder 107)
  - "40-Inch Hydrogen Bubble Chamber Conversion to 70 Kilogauss Superconducting Magnet": proposal III, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 108)
  - Lawrence Radiation Laboratory, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 109)
  - High field chamber, 1969, undated (Box 61, Folder 110-111)
  - "40-Inch Hydrogen Bubble Chamber Conversion to 7.0-Tesla Superconducting Magnet": proposal II, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 112)
  - K2- P proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 113)
  - Chew and Regge theory, 1966, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 114-117)
  - High energy collision studies, 1968-1970 (Box 62, Folder 118)
  - 13 Gev/c K-P event rates and physics programs, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 119)
  - DD production calculation, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 120)
  - "Probing the New Particles with Hadron Beams": Francis Halzen, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 121)
  - D mesons, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 122)
  - 337-363, 1979, undated (Box 62, Folder 123)
  - 346-409, 1979, undated (Box 62, Folder 124)
  - 339-1424, 1979, undated (Box 62, Folder 125)
  - Candidates, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 126)
  - "Proposal to Search for Direct Evidence of Charm in Hadronic Interactions Using a High Resolution Bubble Chamber", 1978 (Box 62, Folder 127)
  - Nucleon decay experiment: L. Sulak, 1979, undated (Box 62, Folder 128)
  - Charm search, systematics, [kinematics?], etc., 1974 (Box 62, Folder 129)
  - Charm search, systematics, [kinematics?], etc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 130)
  - Pais and Trieman, 1977, undated (Box 63, Folder 131)
  - B particle II and III, 1978-1981, undated (Box 63, Folder 132)
  - Quality Monitor Committee and Certification, 1976-1978 (Box 63, Folder 133)
  - Scanning and pre-dig., 1972, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 134)
  - PDP-10 system, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 135)
  - Precision film reader
    - Gilliland-NR, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 136)
    - Hydel, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 137)
    - Franckenstein machine, 1958-1960 (Box 63, Folder 138)
    - Gilliland-NRI, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 139)
    - Copy of contract between Duke University and Gilliland-NRI for manufacture of Franckenstein Measuring Projector I, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 140)
    - Bubble chamber film re-projector, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 141)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1958-1963, undated (Box 63, Folder 142-144)
    - LCSAP, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 145)
  - MAXimization program, undated (Box 63, Folder 146)
  - Program write-ups, 1963-1964, undated (Box 64, Folder 147-149)
  - Event type flow charts, 1961, undated (Box 64, Folder 150)
  - PAY (Willis), undated (Box 64, Folder 151)
  - Notes on YAP, undated (Box 64, Folder 152)
  - PAY-PDP 1, 1960-1965, undated (Box 64, Folder 153-154)
  - PAY for Willis, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 155)
  - YAP, undated (Box 64, Folder 156-158)
  - LEPTON and ALEPT, 1969, undated (Box 65, Folder 159)
  - New TUSER, 1966, undated (Box 65, Folder 160)
  - LUSER, undated (Box 65, Folder 161)
  - AUSER, etc., 1969, undated (Box 65, Folder 162)
  - Gossel's controller test program, undated (Box 65, Folder 163)
  - PNOISE, 1966, undated (Box 65, Folder 164)
  - PDP 6 test programs, 1966, undated (Box 65, Folder 165)
  - Fortran functions, undated (Box 65, Folder 166)
  - Magnetic tape supply, undated (Box 65, Folder 167)
  - PEPR programming notes by J.N. Snyder, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 168)
  - GHIST (Σ -), 1968, undated (Box 65, Folder 169)
  - PDP 6 schedule, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 170)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology PEPR program, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 171-172)
  - TUSER, 1968, undated (Box 65, Folder 173)
  - DTSCAN, 1966, undated (Box 66, Folder 174)
  - Matrix inversion resid. plot, 1965-1968, undated (Box 66, Folder 175)
  - MIT routines, 1966, undated (Box 66, Folder 176)
  - HTMCH, 1967, undated (Box 66, Folder 177)
  - Display manuals routines, undated (Box 66, Folder 178)
  - Old flow charts, 1963-1964, undated (Box 66, Folder 179-180)
  - PUNCH, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 181)
  - Old SPIT, CA/P/T, 1968-1971, undated (Box 66, Folder 182)
  - 370 plot routines, 1972-1975, undated (Box 66, Folder 183)
  - S' plot, 1970-1973, undated (Box 66, Folder 184)
  - Displays, 1966, undated (Box 66, Folder 185)
  - SSC Monte Carlo, 1978, undated (Box 66, Folder 186)
  - CFAKE, 1976, undated (Box 66, Folder 187)
  - Film advance
    - Print format, undated (Box 66, Folder 188)
    - Logic, undated (Box 66, Folder 189)
    - Banks, undated (Box 66, Folder 190)
    - Deuterium, 1959, undated (Box 66, Folder 191)
    - Cascade experiment, undated (Box 66, Folder 192)
    - GUTS, undated (Box 66, Folder 193)
    - Calling sequences, undated (Box 66, Folder 194)
    - 15 track, undated (Box 66, Folder 195)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1958, undated (Box 67, Folder 196)
  - Thesis proposals, 1958-1966, undated (Box 67, Folder 197-200)
  - TV scan, undated (Box 67, Folder 201)
  - SDECAY, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 202)
  - SIGMI. SHUNT. (4x4), 1967-1968 (Box 67, Folder 203)
  - HISTDB, 1968, undated (Box 67, Folder 204)
  - WINDUP, undated (Box 67, Folder 205)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1969-1974, undated (Box 67, Folder 206)
  - Roll 754 frames, undated (Box 67, Folder 207)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1947, 1956-1958, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, undated (Box 67, Folder 208-210)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 68, Folder 211)
  - Summer PEPR help, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 212)
  - GHIST, undated (Box 68, Folder 213)
  - YUPP, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 214)
  - TFLGMT, 1965-1966, undated (Box 68, Folder 215)
  - DIRCHK, undated (Box 68, Folder 216)
  - OPENUP (I, J), 1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 217)
  - OPENUP, undated (Box 68, Folder 218)
  - SAME TK, undated (Box 68, Folder 219)
  - FAKIN J, undated (Box 68, Folder 220)
  - ADDINJ, undated (Box 68, Folder 221)
  - GROUPR, 1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 222)
  - New RDCRD, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 223)
  - Peter's KMTAU and EVSRCH, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 224)
  - FOLLOW, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 225)
  - AJOIN, 1966, undated (Box 68, Folder 226)
  - TKDUMP, undated (Box 68, Folder 227)
  - Operational YUPP, 1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 228)
  - FOLLOW, 1966-1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 229)
  - CUTTRK, 1966-1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 230)
  - GROUPR, undated (Box 68, Folder 231)
  - DBSCAN, undated (Box 68, Folder 232)
  - EVIEV, undated (Box 68, Folder 233)
  - LONG TK, 1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 234)
  - Various time and date routines, 1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 235)
  - END PNT, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 236)
  - KMVEE, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 237)
  - Help, undated (Box 68, Folder 238)
  - ORPICK and VEPARM, 1966, undated (Box 68, Folder 239)
  - TSIGN, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 240)
  - TWO CIR, undated (Box 68, Folder 241)
  - Alvarez group, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 242)
  - KINKCT (Dixon's), 1967 (Box 69, Folder 243)
  - ADDINJ, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 244)
  - SAMETK, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 245)
  - FAKINJ, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 246)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1966-1967, undated (Box 69, Folder 247)
  - GROUPR, 1967, undated (Box 69, Folder 248)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 249)
  - Σ-FY 1968-1969 report, 1968-1969, undated (Box 69, Folder 250)
  - GHIST Σ- (Dixon's), 1968, undated (Box 69, Folder 251)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1975-1980, undated (Box 69, Folder 252-254)
  - Physics courses, 1966-1967, undated (Box 70, Folder 255)
  - MAX, undated (Box 70, Folder 256)
  - Brower stage, 1958, undated (Box 70, Folder 257)
  - DEC tapes and FF directories, 1966-1967, undated (Box 70, Folder 258)
  - TFCTPR, undated (Box 70, Folder 259)
  - PEPR flow charts, 1963-1964, undated (Box 70, Folder 260)
  - CFCAL, undated (Box 70, Folder 261)
  - PEPR banks, 1966, undated (Box 70, Folder 262)
  - GAP distribution, undated (Box 70, Folder 263)
  - TV scan, 1970, undated (Box 70, Folder 264)
  - SLAC-PEPR track, 1969, undated (Box 70, Folder 265)
  - TFPRIP-TFPR2P, undated (Box 70, Folder 266)
  - TFLLUP, 1965-1966, undated (Box 70, Folder 267)
  - TFPRED, 1965-1967 (Box 70, Folder 268)
  - TFPRTK, 1965-1967, undated (Box 70, Folder 269)
  - TPPRH-ionization, 1968, 1973, undated (Box 71, Folder 270)
  - HT TUGP flow charts, 1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 271)
  - Fortran ELREC, 1965, undated (Box 71, Folder 272)